Guide to the Samir Farid Collection AD.MC.011
Akkasah: Center for Photography (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa), 1956; ref85; Mostafa, Niazi
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000007; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 07)
    Hats; Facial Hair; Men; Seas; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Mohamed Hamdy, 1956; ref85_000008; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 08)
    Hats; Facial Hair; Costumes; Negative Images; Actors; Films; Men; Doors/Entrances; Navy; Uniforms; Group Portraits
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000009; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 09)
    Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Ports; Arabic Writing; Costumes; Hats; Group Portraits
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000010; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Hats; Clocks/Watches; Uniforms; Navy; Doors/Entrances; Outdoors; Men; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000011; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Hats; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Navy; Costumes; Weapons; Guns; Men
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000012; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Hats; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Facial Hair; Weapons; Navy; Ports; Costumes; Men; Uniforms
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000013; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Hats; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Ports; Navy; Weapons; Guns; Costumes; Uniforms; Boats/Ships
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000014; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Men; Hats; Cars/Trucks; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000015; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Outdoors; Hats; Navy; Uniforms
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Naeima Wasfi, Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000016; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Hats; Head Covers/Veils; Navy; Women; Boys; Men; Costumes; Uniforms; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Children
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000017; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Hats; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Facial Hair; Costumes; Men
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000018; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Hats; Weapons; Guns; Uniforms; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Actors; Men; Navy
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Zaki Rostom, 1956; ref85_000019; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Arabic Writing; Men; Cars/Trucks; Hats; Turbans; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Outdoors; Doors/Entrances; Transportation
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000020; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Negative Images; Films; Men; Actors; Costumes
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa), 1956; ref85_000021; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Turbans; Hats; Negative Images; Films; Clocks/Watches; Actors; Costumes; Men
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000022; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Hats; Cigarettes; Costumes; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa), 1956; ref85_000023; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Seas; Negative Images; Films; Costumes
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa), 1956; ref85_000024; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 24)
    Men; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Seas; Boats/Ships
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000025; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Weapons; Guns; Negative Images; Films; Hats; Facial Hair; Boats/Ships; Uniforms; Navy; Costumes; Actors; Men
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Anwar Zaky, Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000026; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 26)
    Hats; Boats/Ships; Costumes; Navy; Uniforms; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Ports
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa), 1956; ref85_000027; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 27)
    Hats; Boats/Ships; Cameras; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Seas
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000028; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 28)
    Hats; Navy; Uniforms; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000029; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 29)
    Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Hats; Weapons; Facial Hair; Uniforms; Navy; Guns; Ports; Boats/Ships; Costumes
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Zaki Rostom, 1956; ref85_000030; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 30)
    Turbans; Hats; Prayer Beads; Facial Hair; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Hoda Soltan, Zaki Rostom, 1956; ref85_000031; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 31)
    Fez/Tarboush; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Boys; Turbans; Women; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Children; Hats
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Zaki Rostom, 1956; ref85_000032; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 32)
    Turbans; Facial Hair; Ports; Prayer Beads; Hats; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Mahmoud El Meleigy, Fouad Jaafar, 1956; ref85_000033; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 33)
    Facial Hair; Fez/Tarboush; Weapons; Guns; Cigarettes; Turbans; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Men; Hats
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Solaiman El Gendy, Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000034; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 34)
    Hats; Horses; Guns; Boys; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Birds; Animals; Weapons; Drinks/Beverages; Children
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000035; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 35)
    Hats; Guns; Weapons; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Uniforms; Navy; Costumes; Facial Hair
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Hassan Hamed, Zaki Rostom, 1956; ref85_000036; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 36)
    Prayer Beads; Facial Hair; Cigarettes; Turbans; Hats; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Men
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Hoda Soltan, 1956; ref85_000037; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Turbans; Hats; Head Covers/Veils; Costumes; Jewelry; Women; Men; Films; Actors; Negative Images
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Hoda Soltan, Nahed Abdelaziz, 1956; ref85_000038; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Women; Girls; Turbans; Costumes; Head Covers/Veils
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Nahed Abdelaziz, 1956; ref85_000039; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 39)
    Hats; Head Covers/Veils; Girls; Women; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Navy; Uniforms
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Zaki Rostom, Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000040; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Turbans; Hats; Prayer Beads; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Shisha/Hookah/Nargiles; Men; Films; Actors; Costumes; Drinks/Beverages
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Niazi Mostafa, Farid Shawqy, 1956; ref85_000041; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 41)
    Uniforms; Navy; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Costumes; Palm Trees; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men
  - Platform Number 5 (Rasif rakam khamsa) | Actors in Image: Mohamed Shawky, 1956; ref85_000042; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 42)
    Turbans; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Drinks/Beverages; Guns; Men; Costumes; Facial Hair; Weapons; Telephones; Tea/Coffee
- The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau), 1956; ref87; 4717; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Abdelsalam El Nabolsi, 1956; ref87_000001; 4718; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 43)
    Negative Images; Uniforms; Hats; Facial Hair; Films; Actors; Men; Military/Soldiers; Costumes
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Abdelsalam El Nabolsi, Monera Sonbul, 1956; ref87_000002; 4719; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 44)
    Men; Facial Hair; Hats; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Women; Costumes; Jewelry
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Ahmad Ramzy, 1956; ref87_000003; 4720; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 45)
    Costumes; Actors; Films; Negative Images; Hats; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Men
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau), 1956; ref87_000004; 4721; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 46)
    Uniforms; Films; Negative Images; Clocks/Watches; Hats; Actors; Wars; Military/Soldiers; Men
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Said Abou Bakr, 1956; ref87_000005; 4722; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 47)
    Hats; Men; Films; Actors; Uniforms; Negative Images; Costumes; Military/Soldiers
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Ahmad Ramzy, 1956; ref87_000006; 4723; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 48)
    Men; Films; Actors; Negative Images; Hats; Costumes; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Ahmad Ramzy, 1956; ref87_000007; 4724; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 49)
    Men; Girls; Military/Soldiers; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Uniforms; Costumes; Children
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Amal Farid, Ahmad Ramzy, 1956; ref87_000008; 4725; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 50)
    Hats; Men; Films; Negative Images; Actors; Women; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Costumes; Medals/Insignia
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Monera Sonbul, 1956; ref87_000009; 4726; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 51)
    Men; Women; Actors; Films; Negative Images; Facial Hair; Costumes; Uniforms; Jewelry; Hats; Group Portraits; Workers
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Ahmad Ramzy, Amal Farid, 1956; ref87_000010; 4727; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 52)
    Men; Women; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Uniforms; Hats; Gloves; Costumes; Outdoors; Military/Soldiers
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Amal Farid, Ahmad Ramzy, 1956; ref87_000011; 4728; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 53)
    Drinks/Beverages; Women; Men; Costumes; Uniforms; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Bags/Purses; Gloves; Group Portraits; Military/Soldiers
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Amal Farid, 1956; ref87_000012; 4729; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 54)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Jewelry; Costumes
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Shokry Sarhan, 1956; ref87_000013; 4730; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 55)
    Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Costumes; Men; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Outdoors; Hats
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Ahmad Ramzy, Abdelsalam El Nabolsi, 1956; ref87_000014; 4731; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 56)
    Men; Actors; Films; Negative Images; Facial Hair; Hats; Airplanes; Workers; Uniforms; Costumes; Group Portraits
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Abdelsalam El Nabolsi, Said Abou Bakr, Adly Kasseb, 1956; ref87_000015; 4732; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 57)
    Men; Hats; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Clocks/Watches
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Salwa Mahmoud, Mohamed Abdel Moteleb, 1956; ref87_000016; 4733; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 58)
    Turbans; Fez/Tarboush; Flags; Belly Dancers; Jewelry; Weapons; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Umbrellas/Parasols; Outdoors; Men; Women; Hats
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Adly Kasseb, 1956; ref87_000017; 4734; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 59)
    Facial Hair; Men; Costumes; Negative Images; Hats; Uniforms; Actors; Films; Airplanes; Group Portraits; Workers
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Ahmad Ramzy, 1956; ref87_000018; 4735; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 60)
    Men; Actors; Films; Negative Images; Costumes; Outdoors
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Amal Farid, 1956; ref87_000019; 4736; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 61)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Outdoors; Rivers; Lakes
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Ahmad Ramzy, 1956; ref87_000020; 4737; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 62)
    Men; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Uniforms; Outdoors; Individual Portraits; Workers
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau), 1956; ref87_000021; 4738; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 63)
    Men; Fez/Tarboush; Costumes; Hats; Facial Hair; Weapons; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Turbans; Actors; Negative Images; Films
  - The Sky Devils (Shayatine el jau) | Actors in Image: Abdelsalam El Nabolsi, 1956; ref87_000022; 4739; Mostafa, Niazi; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 12, Folder 64)
    Facial Hair; Hats; Uniforms; Airplanes; Costumes; Men; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Group Portraits
- Unsatisfied Hearts, 1956; ref88
  - Unsatisfied Hearts | Actors in Image: Kamal El Shennawy, Zahrat Al Oula, 1956; ref88_000001; Omara, Ibrahim; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 12, Folder 65)
    Men; Facial Hair; Women; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Facial Hair
- Lover's Walk, 1957; ref89; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Lover's Walk | Actors in Image: Shokry Sarhan, Mariem Fakhr Eldin, 1957; ref89_000001; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 12, Folder 66)
    Motorcycles; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Outdoors; Clocks/Watches; Costumes; Women
  - Lover's Walk | Actors in Image: Mariem Fakhr Eldin, Mohammed Almogi, Youssef Fakhr El Din, Shokry Sarhan, Samira Ahmed, 1957; ref89_000002; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 12, Folder 67)
    Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Facial Hair; Costumes; Tents; Women
  - Lover's Walk | Actors in Image: Thuraya Fakhry, Shokry Sarhan, 1957; ref89_000003; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 12, Folder 68)
    Head Covers/Veils; Clocks/Watches; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Women; Men; Costumes
  - Lover's Walk | Actors in Image: Shokry Sarhan, Mariem Fakhr Eldin, 1957; ref89_000004; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud; 1 negatives; 57 x 57 cm (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Fearful Night, 1957; ref90; Bedeer, Sayed
  - Fearful Night, 1957; ref90_000001; Bedeer, Sayed; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Fearful Night, 1957; ref90_000002; Bedeer, Sayed; 1 negatives; 57 x 88 cm (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Hamido's Son, 1957; ref91; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - Hamido's Son | Actors in Image: Ismail Yasin, Tawfik El Deken, 1957; ref91_000001; Abdel Wahab, Fateen; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - Hamido's Son | Actors in Image: Ismail Yasin, Zinat Sedki, 1957; ref91_000002; Abdel Wahab, Fateen; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Hats; Women; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Jewelry; Men; Actors
  - Hamido's Son | Actors in Image: Ahmad Ramzy, Ismail Yasin, 1957; ref91_000003; Abdel Wahab, Fateen; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Hats; Costumes; Beaches; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits
  - Hamido's Son | Actors in Image: Ahmad Ramzy, Nelly Mazlom, 1957; ref91_000004; Abdel Wahab, Fateen; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Costumes; Beaches; Palm Trees
  - Hamido's Son | Actors in Image: Abd El Fatah El Quossary, Ahmad Ramzy, 1957; ref91_000005; Abdel Wahab, Fateen; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Turbans; Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Men
  - Hamido's Son | Actors in Image: Hend Rostom, 1957; ref91_000006; Abdel Wahab, Fateen; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Fish
  - Hamido's Son, 1957; ref91_000007; Abdel Wahab, Fateen; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 9)
- The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt), 1957; ref92; al Sheikh, Kamal
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt) | Actors in Image: Eman, Mahmoud El Meleigy, 1957; ref92_000001; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Lab Coats
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt), 1957; ref92_000002; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt) | Actors in Image: Roshdy Abaza, Mahmoud El Meleigy, 1957; ref92_000003; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Facial Hair; Men; Costumes; Films; Actors; Negative Images
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Roshdy Abaza, 1957; ref92_000004; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Facial Hair; Cars/Trucks; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Weapons; Men; Actors; Guns; Transportation
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Eman, 1957; ref92_000005; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Men
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt) | Actors in Image: Eman, Ahmed Loxer, Farid Shawqy, Said Abou Bakr, 1957; ref92_000006; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Telephones; Men; Uniforms; Lanterns/Lamps; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Women; Clocks/Watches; Furnishings; Military/Soldiers
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt) | Actors in Image: Ahmed Loxer, Said Abou Bakr, Eman, Farid Shawqy, 1957; ref92_000007; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Facial Hair; Pens/Inkwells; Hats; Uniforms; Men; Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Military/Soldiers
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Eman, 1957; ref92_000008; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Clocks/Watches; Women; Negative Images; Men; Films; Actors; Costumes
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt) | Actors in Image: Roshdy Abaza, 1957; ref92_000009; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 18)
    Facial Hair; Guns; Weapons; Costumes; Films; Actors; Negative Images; Men
  - The Merchants of Death (Toggar el mawt) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Eman, 1957; ref92_000010; al Sheikh, Kamal; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Costumes; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Telephones; Women
- The Thug (El Fetewa), 1957; ref93; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqi, Taheyya Kariokka, 1957; ref93_000001; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Hats; Facial Hair; Women; Clocks/Watches; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men
  - The Thug (El Fetewa), 1957; ref93_000002; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 21)
    Hats; Boys; Men; Negative Images; Films; Costumes; Actors; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Children
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqi, Taheyya Kariokka, 1957; ref93_000003; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Men; Hats; Women; Head Covers/Veils
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Zaki Rostom, Farid Shawqy, Tawfik El Deken, 1957; ref93_000004; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Turbans; Facial Hair; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Men; Guns; Weapons
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Tawfik El Deken, Zaki Rostom, 1957; ref93_000005; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 24)
    Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Weapons; Guns; Turbans; Men; Actors; Costumes; Films; Negative Images; Outdoors
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Taheyya Kariokka, Farid Shawqy, 1957; ref93_000006; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 25)
    Turbans; Bags/Purses; Costumes; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Women; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Outdoors
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Taheyya Kariokka, Farid Shawqy, 1957; ref93_000007; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 26)
    Facial Hair; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Bags/Purses; Head Covers/Veils; Costumes; Turbans; Women; Men; Outdoors
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Taheyya Kariokka, Farid Shawqy, 1957; ref93_000008; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Pyramids; Turbans; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Men; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Saqqara, Egypt
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1957; ref93_000009; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 28)
    Turbans; Facial Hair; Costumes; Camels; Actors; Negative Images; Films; Men; Outdoors; Pyramids
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1957; ref93_000010; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 29)
    Fez/Tarboush; Turbans; Canes/Walking Sticks; Facial Hair; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Food; Hats
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, Mohamed Reda, 1957; ref93_000011; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Turbans; Facial Hair; Fez/Tarboush; Costumes; Men; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Food; Hats
  - The Thug (El Fetewa) | Actors in Image: Farid Shawqy, 1957; ref93_000012; Abu Seif, Salah; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 13, Folder 31)
    Men; Negative Images; Films; Hats; Turbans; Facial Hair; Telephones; Actors; Costumes